{"teammembers":[
    {
        "id": "1",
        "Question":"Question 1 of 10",
        "Q":"What does CSS stand for?",
        "Options":["Cascading Style Sheets","Computer Style Sheets","Creative Style Sheets",""],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "2",
        "Question":"Question 2 of 10",
        "Q":"What is the correct HTML for referring to an external style sheet?",
        "Options":[" &lt; stylesheet &gt; mystyle.css &lt;/stylesheet &gt;","&lt; style src='mystyle.css'&gt;","&lt; link rel='stylesheet' type='text/css' href='mystyle.css' &gt;",""],
        "Answer":2
    },
    {
        "id": "3",
        "Question":"Question 3 of 10",
        "Q":"Where in an HTML document is the correct place to refer to an external style sheet?",
        "Options":["In the &lt; head &gt; section","At the end of the document","In the &lt; body &gt; section",""],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "4",
        "Question":"Question 4 of 10",
        "Q":"Which HTML tag is used to define an internal style sheet?",
        "Options":["&lt;script &gt; ","&lt; style &gt;","&lt; css &gt;",""],
        "Answer":1
    },
    {
        "id": "5",
        "Question":"Question 5 of 10",
        "Q":"Which HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?",
        "Options":["style","font","class","src"],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "6",
        "Question":"Question 6 of 10",
        "Q":"Which is the correct CSS syntax?",
        "Options":["body{ color:black;}","{body:color=black;}","{body;color:black;}","body:color=black"],
        "Answer":0
    },
    {
        "id": "7",
        "Question":"Question 7 of 10",
        "Q":"Which property is used to change the background color?",
        "Options":["color","background-color","bgcolor",""],
        "Answer":1
    },
    {
        "id": "8",
        "Question":"Question 8 of 10",
        "Q":"Which CSS property is used to change the text color of an element?",
        "Options":["color","text-color","fgcolor",""],
        "Answer":1
    },
    {
        "id": "9",
        "Question":"Question 9 of 10",
        "Q":"Which CSS property controls the text size?",
        "Options":["text-size","text-style","font-style","font-size"],
        "Answer":3
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "Question":"Question 10 of 10",
        "Q":"How do you make each word in a text start with a capital letter?",
        "Options":["text-transform:capitalize","You can't do that with css","transform:capitalize",""],
        "Answer":0
    }

]}